He never wanted to be the hero
The Ballad of Lefty Brown is a western film directed by Jared Moshé.
Aging sidekick Lefty Brown has ridden with Eddie Johnson his entire life.
But when a rustler kills Eddie, Lefty is forced from his partner’s shadow
and must confront the ugly realities of frontier justice.
Lefty Brown, played by Bill Pullman.
Edward Johnson, played by Peter Fonda.
Laura Johnson, played by Kathy Baker.
Jimmy Bierce, played by Jim Caviezel.
Tom Harrah, played by Tommy Flanagan.
Jeremiah, played by Diego Josef.
The Ballad of Lefty Brown is a 2017 American western action
film written and directed by Jared Moshe.
Starring Bill Pullman, Kathy Baker, Jim Caviezel, Tommy Flanagan, and Peter Fonda, the film follows Lefty Brown (Pullman), a Montana
frontiersman seeking vengeance against the outlaws who murdered his friend, the newly elected Senator Edward Johnson (Fonda).
The Ballad of Lefty Brown premiered at South by Southwest on March 11, 2017, and
was theatrically released in the United States on December 15, 2017.
Despite underperforming commercially, the film received critical
acclaim, with particular praise for Pullman's performance.
The film explores themes of ambush, alcoholic, frontier
justice, political expediency, a decent man.